https://irosacea.org/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. Your privacy is of utmost concern to us and we will never disclose any of your contact information to anyone without your permission unless we are legally bound by law to do so. If you are still concerned about your privacy please read this post that is designed to address your concerns. Our Guidelines explain clearly the Terms and Conditions of using the Rosacea Research & Development Institute Member Web Site Forum, Blog, Club, and Gallery.
Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web servers.
Our Commitment to Children's Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
Cookies
This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.
Legal Disclaimer
You may review the complete privacy policy by reading the Legal Disclaimer.
RRDi Member Forum, PO Box 858, Centre, Alabama, 95960
Third Parties
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.
Privacy Policy
Spam Defense
The IPS Spam Defense Service passes the email address and IP address of the registering member to the service to determine the likelihood a registering account is a spam source.
Privacy Policy
Invisible reCAPTCHA
This site uses a CAPTCHA to ensure humans are performing certain actions. The CAPTCHA provider may set a session cookie and get information about your internet browser and device accessing this website.
Privacy Policy
All Posts
All Activity
Forum Home
Privacy Policy
×
Existing user? Sign In
Sign Up
Create New...
